CHASE ALBRIGHT

INTERNSHIP

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Hard-working Computer Engineering major (3.7 GPA) currently attending Texas A&M University, with 10 months of work experience. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of application development and emerging technologies skills to successfully fill the Internship role at your company. Frequently praised as adaptable by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

DataGumbo, Houston, TX / May 2021 - Aug 2021

- Used React to build a UI for an internal tool
- Created APIs for interacting with the blockchain using Golang
- Experience with blockchain and its architecture

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN

4-Tower, Houston, TX / Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

- Used Angular to create features within a web app
- Used CSS and Bootstrap to style components and fix bugs
- · Did research to find potential clients and product data

DATA ANALYST INTERN

Genscape, Sugarland, TX / Jun 2018 - Aug 2018

- Used python create a machine learning program to count Tesla cars
- Processed and analyzed data in Excel to make into a report for customers
- Analyzed video footage to count Tesla cars being shipped out of the factory

WEBSITE

Please check out my personal website located at https://chasealbright.com in order to get more information about me!

- chasemalbright33@gmail.com
- (713) 504-0132
- 3100 PRECINCT LINE RD, RICHMOND, TX, 77406

EDUCATION

TEXAS A&M UNIVERSITY GPA: 3.7

College Station, TX

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Computer Engineering Candidate (Expected graduation May 2024) Extracurricular Activities

- Freshman Reaching Excellence in Engineering (FREE)
- Baseball Coaching

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

React JS

Javascript

Golang

Python

Git

Bitbucket/SourceTree

Firebase

MongoDB

C++